cozycot.com 2010-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Shopping Spree, Women Forums, Beauty Tips, Product Reviews | CozyCot

COZYCOT PTE LTD - PRIVACY POLICY 

Your privacy is important, so CozyCot Pte Ltd has created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit the CozyCot web site (the "Site"), why we collect it, and how it is used. 

The terms "you," "your" and "yours" refer to all visitors of our Site. The terms "CozyCot", "we", "us" and "our" refer to CozyCot Pte Ltd and its subsidiaries and affiliates. This Privacy Policy is governed by our "Terms of Use". By accessing this Site and the content, information, products and services available on this Site (collectively the "Service"), you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes, so we encourage you to visit this page often. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

1.      **Information We Collect; How We Collect It**

We may request at times that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. Such personal information includes any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number(s) and other contact information, as well as physical traits and allergies in the "My Profile." Generally some or all of this information is requested when you register on the Site, when you post product reviews or forums, or when you provide information in connection with giveaways, contests and surveys. We may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information as well as public information such as user ratings and reviews and other information you view on the Site. 

Some of the information CozyCot collects is not explicitly submitted by you -- CozyCot also automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, the web pages you request, your browser type and language, access times, and the referring web site address. 

For instance, when you visit our Site, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our Site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our Site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on the Site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our Site. 

We also may use standard other technologies, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our Site. We also may include web beacons in promotional or other e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our Site users to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Site uses information derived from your visits to this Site to target advertising within this Site and gauge the effectiveness of the advertising. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this Site and other web sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your browser. In addition, we may use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Site, and to learn which banner ads bring users to our Site.

2.      **How We Use Your Information**

Generally, we may use information that we collect about you to:

o        deliver the products and services that you have requested;

o        manage your account and provide you with customer support;

o        perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our service, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;

o        communicate with you by e-mail about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;

o        develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other web sites;

o        verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and giveaways;

o        enforce our terms and conditions;

o        give away product samples to users who are willing to have their personal information shared with the product manufacturers;

o        manage our business; and

o        perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

Information such as your full name, profile photo and any personally identifiable information you have included in your reviews may be shown to other users primarily in conjunction with product reviews and ratings you have contributed. In addition, we may sell or license your reviews to third parties, in which case your first name and last initial and any personally identifiable information you have included in your reviews may be shown to users of such third party web sites. Your postings will be displayed on publicly-viewable web pages, and whenever you disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

3.      **How We Share or Disclose Your Information**

We may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our Site or while using our Service under the following circumstances. 

_Personal Information_

We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. 

We may share your personal information in connection with sharing, selling or licensing your product reviews to third parties. Your first name and last initial, profile photo, and any personally identifiable information you have included in your reviews may be transferred to such third parties and displayed on their web sites in connection with such third parties' publication of your reviews. 

We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include supporting our Site functionality and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Site. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. 

We also may disclose your personal information in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 

We may disclose your personal information when we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our Site's terms and conditions or other agreements or policies. 

We may disclose your personal information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. The personal information which you provide to us is an asset of CozyCot and may be included in the assets transferred in the event of a substantial corporate transaction. 

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the web sites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the Singapore. 

CozyCot will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

_Aggregated and Non-Personal Information_

We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Site and on third-party web sites. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our Site and the most popular areas and features of our Site. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop content and new services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising. 

_Other_

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Site periodically.

4.      **Release of Personally Identifiable Information**

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

**We may share your information with CozySpree Merchants**. From time to time, we provide offers from particular Merchants (referred to as “CozySpree Merchants”) who, as part of the offer, request information on CozySpree customers who purchased the offer. In those cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with CozySpree Merchants. Sharing this Information will allow a CozySpree Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a CozySpree Merchant if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the CozySpree Merchant involved in that Identification Activity. Please note that we will only provide a CozySpree Merchant your information with an opt-in notice to you, in which you will have a chance to choose that CozySpree and not give the CozySpree Merchant your personal information. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such CozySpree Merchant. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with CozySpree, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the CozySpree Merchant, and the actions of the CozySpree Merchant are not in our control.

**We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers**. We provide services and products through third parties. These “Third Party Service Providers” perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies (“Affiliates”) with whom we have business relationships and may share your information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a service, we release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the service and, if applicable, release your address to the delivery service to deliver the service. Likewise, we may release an Affiliate’s information to our bank to send out a payment. We encourage CozySpree Merchants and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.

**We may remarket your information**. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with the CozyCot website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by CozyCot to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show CozyCot ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to CozyCot's website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

**We may share your information in a Business Transfer**. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

**We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others**. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

5.      **Product Reviews and Ratings and Forums**

We encourage you to generate and submit product reviews and ratings regarding beauty products on our Site. Our Site also features areas where you may access other interactive features such as forums. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other web sites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

6.      **Third Party Web Site**

There are a number of places on our Site where you may click on a hyperlink to access other web sites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our Site, you may be taken to a web site that we do not control. These third-party web sites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those web sites. We recommend that you consult the privacy policies of all third-party web sites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the web page you are visiting.

7.      **Controlling Your Personal Information**

You may elect not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Site because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member or user; submit product ratings and reviews; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or giveaways; ask a question; or initiate certain other transactions on our Site. 

If you are a registered user of our Site, you may update your personal information simply by signing in and going to "Edit Profile" from our home page. You can make changes to your account information at any time. To protect your privacy and security, we will also verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You may also contact us to communicate any questions or concerns. More information about how to contact us is provided below. 

At any time you can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from us by logging in with your account information, clicking on the "Edit Profile" link, then clicking on the "My Account" link and adjusting those items of your communication settings you would like to update. You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. We may however send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

8.      **How we protect your personal information**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For instance, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. However, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.

9.      **Children's privacy**

Our Site is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

10.  **Visiting from outside the Singapore**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our Site from residents of the Singapore. If you are visiting our Site from outside the Singapore, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the Singapore where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the Singapore and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

11.  **Contacting CozyCot**

Our goal is to respect your privacy. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at [support@cozycot.com](mailto:support@cozycot.com) or by postal mail to: 

CozyCot Pte Ltd,   
VBox 888899  
Singapore 919191  
Attn: Privacy Officer 

CozyCot welcomes your comments and questions.

_Last updated on June 2, 2010_  
© 2010 CozyCot Pte Ltd All rights reserved.
